Wey Gu Software Developer



About me

Working on OpenStack related development stuff at Ericsson, based in Shanghai, I like to build things, do troubleshoot and code in Python. I am open to opportunities for building good things with great guys.

I grew up in China (Mandarin) and had worked globally for remote and onsite (English).

Skills

Python

OpenStack

FullStack

Linux

Contact



Changning, 88 Huichuan Rd.



✓ littlewey@gmail.com



(86) 150-4242-7363



https://note.siwei.info



littlewey



Experience

Software Developer

Ericsson

Since Aug. 2018

Developer at Cloud R&D Unit.

Cloud Engineer

Ericsson

Sept. 2016 - Aug. 2018

Cloud Troubleshooter for global customers. Tier 3 Support/Troubleshoot on OpenStack for half a year. Tool/DevOps Developer.

Telco. Integration Engineer

Ericsson

June 2011 - Sept. 2016

Integration & verification on circuit switch core network (3G), Tool Developer.



Education

Bachelor of Mathematics

September 2007 - June 2011

Majored in Math & Applied Math, Dalian University of Technology.

<>> Projects

Resource Board

Vue, Flask, PostgreSQL, K8s, Redis

Working in progress; A scalable web app side project built with Flask socketio & Vue.js. Targeting to build a distributed system for fun yet helping improve team collaboration.

Cloud ML-**ResourceOpt**

Bayesian Optimization, Heat, Ansible

Working in progress; As the initiator and the driver of PoC on using ML(BO) to help optimize OpenStack. This project is aiming to output a toolchain and methodology to help optimize the OpenStack resource placement weighing policy for given benchmark.

Telco. laaS OpenStack, MOS 9

for Mitaka SW Developer on OpenStack, troubleshoot and feature design/ development.